Guide to Arizona State University Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00085
Cubberley Education Library
Arizona State University (formerly Arizona State College, Tempe, formerly Arizona State Teachers College at Tempe, formerly Tempe State Teachers College, formerly Tempe Normal School of Arizona, formerly Normal School of Arizona at Tempe, formerly Arizona Territorial Normal School)
1890-1977
Cubberley Education Library
Cubb.00085
83 item(s)
Located in Tempe, Arizona. Established as territorial Normal School 1885. Changed name to Arizona Territorial Normal School in 1889 then Normal School of Arizona in 1896. Became Tempe Normal School of Arizona in 1903 and then Tempe State Teachers College in 1925 and Arizona State Teachers College at Tempe in 1930. Name changed to Arizona State College at Tempe in 1945. Became Arizona State University in 1958 and Arizona State University Main in 1996, then Arizona State University at the Tempe Campus in 2004. Reverted to Arizona State University in 2006.
Teachers colleges; Arizona
- Arizona Territorial Normal School, 1890-1898; 7 item(s) Catalogs for 1890/91-1891/92, 1893/94, 1896/97-1897/98
  - Biennial Report of the Normal School, 1891-1898; 2 item(s) Reports for 1891/92 & 1897/98
- Normal School of Arizona at Tempe, 1898-1902; 3 item(s) Catalogs for 1898 (title on cover is Arizona Normal School), 1900, 1902
- Tempe Normal School of Arizona, 1905-1924; 13 item(s) Catalogs for 1905/06, 1907/08, 1909/10-1914/15 Bulletins for 1915, 1917, 1919, 1923
- Tempe State Teachers College, 1925-1929; 5 item(s) Bulletins for 1925-1929
- Arizona State Teachers College at Tempe, 1930-1945; 13 item(s) Catalogs for 1930/31-1939/40, 1941/43, 1944/45
- Arizona State College, Tempe, 1945-1959; 16 item(s) Catalogs for 1945/46-1949/50, 1951/52-1955/57
  - Arizona State College, Tempe Graduate Division, 1950-1959; 4 item(s) Catalogs for 1950, 1955/56, 1957/58-1958/59
  - Delinquency Control Institute, Summer 1955; 1 item(s)
  - Arizona State Teachers College Art, 1932; 1 item(s)
- Arizona State University, 1959-1977; 26 item(s) Catalogs for 1959/61-1967/69, 1971/73, 1976/77 Supplement to 1963/65
  - Arizona State University Graduate College, 1959-1977; 8 item(s) Catalogs for 1959/61-1963/64, 1965/67-1971/73, 1975/77
  - Arizona State University Report of the President, 1961-1972; 10 item(s) Reports for 1961/62-1966/67, 1968/69-1971/72